<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<root>
	<questions>
    <question id="EndorsementDetails.ExcessData" label="Excess">
      <helpText title="Excess">
        <![CDATA[
      An excess is an amount which you may have to contribute towards your claim. 
      The acceptance of a claim is subject to the payment of any applicable excesses. 
      If you vary your excess, your insurance premium will change. Please also note the ‘Excesses’ section on your Policy Portfolio.
      ]]>
      </helpText>
    </question>

	<question id="Email" label="Please provide your email address to receive your new Policy Schedule as confirmation of your changes." watermark="Email address">
      <errors>
        <add key="Required" value="Please enter an email address to receive your new Policy Schedule as confirmation of your change." />
        <add key="StringTooLong" value="Email address is too long. (Maximum is 50 characters)." />
      </errors>
    
		<helpText title="Email confirmation">
			<![CDATA[If you do not wish to provide an email address please call us on <b class="u-noWrap">1300 657 627</b> to complete the change to your policy.]]>
		</helpText>
	</question>


	  <question id="EndorsementDetails.HireCarAfterAccident" label="Add hire car after accident?">
      <helpText title="Hire car after accident">
        <![CDATA[
        Your policy includes an unlimited hire car after fire, theft and attempted theft as standard. 
		You can also choose to extend this cover to include an unlimited hire car after accident. 
		The hire car will be provided for an unlimited number of days until your car is fixed or your claim is settled.
        ]]>
      </helpText>
    </question>	  
	  
    <question id="EndorsementDetails.ProtectNoClaimBonus" label="Add no claim bonus protection?">
      <helpText title="No claim bonus protection">
        <![CDATA[                    
		If you are on the maximum no claim bonus you can protect your bonus for an additional cost. 
		This means you retain your maximum no claim bonus even if you make one at fault claim per year. 
        ]]>
      </helpText>
    </question>

    <question id="EndorsementDetails.SumInsured" label="Agreed value">
      <helpText title="Agreed value">
        <![CDATA[
        The agreed value is the amount we agree to insure your vehicle for.  
        The agreed value includes GST, registration, any other ‘on-road’ costs and accessories fitted to your vehicle.  
        You may choose to increase or decrease the agreed value of your car between the range provided.
        ]]>
      </helpText>
    </question>

  </questions>
</root>